A Guide to the Directors' Correspondence of the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1933-1977 (bulk 1934-1976)
Library of Virginia
- Theatre: General, 1952-1960 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Theatre: General, 1959-1969 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Theatre: General, 1961-1964 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Theatre: General, 1962-1969 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Theatre: General, 1967-1975 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Theatre: General, 1969-1970 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Theatre: General, 1970-1971 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Theatre: General, 1970-1973 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Theatre: General 1972-1973 Season, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Theatre: General, 1974-1975 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Theatre: General, 1975-1976 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Theatre: Governor, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Theatre: Great Divide, The, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Theatre: HMS Pinafore, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Theatre: Hosho No - Performance, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 15)
- Theatre: Imaginary Invalid, The, 1957-1958 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Theatre: Inherit the Wind, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Theatre: Inspector General, The, 1957 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Theatre: Juno and the Paycock, 1957 (Box 59, Folder 19)
- Theatre: Knack, The, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 20)
- Theatre: Lute Song, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 21)
- Theatre: Major Barbara, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 22)
- Theatre: Marat/Sade, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 23)
- Theatre: Marat/Sade - Reactions, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Theatre: Music Lecture Series, 1958-1959 (Box 59, Folder 25)
- Theatre: Music Lecture Series, 1958-1961 (Box 59, Folder 26)
- Theatre: Musical Programs - Information, 1950-1954 (Box 59, Folder 27)
- Theatre: Our Town, 1957-1958 (Box 59, Folder 28)
- Theatre: Play Season 1957/58. 1957-1958 (Box 59, Folder 29)
- Theatre: Play Suggestions, 1954-1958 (Box 59, Folder 30)
- Theatre: Play Suggestions, 1954-1958 (OVERSIZE) (Box 86, Folder 7)
- Theatre: Productions 1959/60, 1959-1960 (Box 59, Folder 31)
- Theatre: Productions 1961/62, 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 32)
- Theatre: Productions 1962/63, 1962-1963 (Box 59, Folder 33)
- Theatre: Productions 1963/64, 1963-1964 (Box 59, Folder 34)
- Theatre: Productions 1964/65, 1964-1965 (Box 59, Folder 35)
- Theatre: Productions 1965/66, 1965-1966 (Box 59, Folder 36)
- Theatre: Productions 1966/67, 1966-1967 (Box 59, Folder 37)
- Theatre: Productions 1970/71, 1970-1971 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Theatre: Productions 1971/72, 1971-1972 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Theatre: Productions 1972/73, 1972-1973 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Theatre: Promotion 1957/58 Season, 1957 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Theatre: Rashomon, 1961 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Theatre: Records, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Theatre: Richmond Chamber Music Society, 1956-1959 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Theatre: Richmond Chamber Music Society - Underwriters 1956/57 Season, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Theatre: Richmond Dance Society, 1955-1960 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Theatre: Richmond Dance Society - Underwriters 1956/57 Season, 1956-1957 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Theatre: Rockefeller, 1955 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Theatre: Rockefeller Productions - Enchanted Treasure 1958 February 15, 1957-1958 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Theatre: R.U.R., 1959 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Theatre: Segregation, 1954-1963 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Theatre: She Stoops to Conquer, 1961 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Theatre: Shoemaker's Prodigious Wife, The, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Theatre: Six Degrees of Crime, The, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Theatre: Sound System, 1956-1957 (Box 60, Folder 18)
- Theatre: Survey, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 19)
- Theatre: Tellford, 1963-1965 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Theatre: Treat - The Gallows Man, 1958 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Theatre: Virginia Composers Festival Concert 1960 April 17, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 22)
- Theatre: Waltz of the Toreadors, The - Fate of, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 23)
- Theatre: Women, The, 1967-1968 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Time Traveling Exhibit, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 25)
- Time Traveling Exhibit, 1947 (OVERSIZE) (Box 86, Folder 8)
- Toronto, Art Gallery of, 1950-1964 (Box 60, Folder 26)
- Toronto, Art Gallery of, 1950-1964 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 112)
- Travel: Blacksburg, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 27)
- Travel: Bristol, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 28)
- Travel: Charlotte Court House, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 29)
- Travel: Culpeper, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 30)
- Travel: Gloucester, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 31)
- Travel: Leesburg, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 32)
- Travel: Lynchburg, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 33)
- Travel: Newport News, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 34)
- Travel: Norfolk, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 35)
- Travel: Roanoke, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 36)
- Travel: Waynesboro, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 37)
- Travel: Williamsburg, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 40)
- Travel: Williamsburg, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 38)
- Travel: Winchester, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 39)
- Traveling Exhibitions: Proposal, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 40)
- Traveling Exhibitions: Service Reports, 1952-1953, folder 1 of 3 (Box 60, Folder 41)
- Traveling Exhibitions: Service Reports, 1952-1953, folder 2 of 3 (Box 60, Folder 42)
- Traveling Exhibitions: Service Reports, 1952-1953, folder 3 of 3 (Box 60, Folder 43)
- Travels: Museums, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 44)
- Trigere, Pauline, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 45)
- Trip: World's Fair, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 46)
- Trustees, 1963-1973 (OVERSIZE) (Box 86, Folder 9)
- Trustees: General Prospects, 1963-1973 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Trustees: Lists and Committees, 1971-1976 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Trustees: Special Fund, 1971-1974 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Trustees: Youth Guild, 1971-1975 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Tuck, William M., 1951-1964 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Tuck, William M.: Clippings, 1946-1950 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Tunnard, Christopher, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Twentieth Century Gallery, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Twery, Elliott, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Two Days in November, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- U: General, 1940 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- U: General, 1951-1972 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- U: General, 1951-1972 (OVERSIZE) (Box 86, Folder 10)
- UNESCO: Correspondence, 1945-1965 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- UNESCO: Correspondence, 1945-1965 (OVERSIZE) (Box 86, Folder 11)
- UNESCO: Denver Meeting, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- UNESCO: Slides, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- United Daughters of the Confederacy, 1957-1962 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- United Givers Fund: Board of Directors, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 17)
- United Givers Fund: Board of Directors, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 18)
- United States Air Force Academy: Fine Arts Advisory Committee, 1958-1963 (Box 61, Folder 19)
- United States Air Force Academy: Fine Arts Advisory Committee, 1958-1963 (RESTRICTED OVERSIZE) (Box 88, Folder 5)
- United States Air Force Academy: Fine Arts Advisory Committee, 1958-1963 (SLIDES) (Box 89, Folder 14-16)
- United States Information Agency, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 20)
- United States Information Agency: Voice of America, 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 21)
- United States National Committee for the Preservation of the Nubian Monuments, 1959-1963 (Box 61, Folder 22)
- United States Savings Bonds, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 23)
- University Center in Virginia, Inc., 1954-1966 (Box 61, Folder 24)
- University of Virginia, 1935-1945 (Box 61, Folder 25)
- University of Virginia, 1935-1945 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 113)
- University of Virginia, 1960-1972 (Box 61, Folder 26)
- University of Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1947-1960 (Box 61, Folder 27)
- University of Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1947-1960 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 114)
- V: General, 1934-1940 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- V: General, 1958-1972 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- V: General, 1958-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 115)
- V: General, 1973-1976 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- V: General, 1973-1976 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 116)
- Vacations, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Valentine Museum, 1969-1974 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Van Wagenen, Elizabeth, 1934-1937 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Van Weeren-Griek, Hans, 1940-1944 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Vandalism, 1958-1959 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Velz, Richard A., 1949-1955 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Velz, Richard A., 1955-1957 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Velz, Richard A., 1957 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Viennese Ball 1965, 1964-1966 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Viennese Ball 1967: Committees, 1966-1967 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Virginia Antiques Fair, 1952 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- Virginia Art Alliance, 1933-1945 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Virginia Art Alliance, 1934-1940 (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Virginia Art Alliance, 1935-1945 (Box 62, Folder 17)
- Virginia Art Alliance, 1941-1942 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- Virginia Art Alliance, 1941-1942 (OVERSIZE) (Box 86, Folder 12)
- Virginia Art Alliance, 1942-1943 (Box 62, Folder 19)
- Virginia Art Alliance, 1944 (Box 62, Folder 20)
- Virginia Art Alliance, 1949 (Box 62, Folder 21)
- Virginia Art Alliance, 1951-1953 (Box 62, Folder 22)
- Virginia Art Alliance, 1954-1956 (Box 62, Folder 23)
- Virginia Art Alliance, 1958 (Box 62, Folder 24)
- Virginia Art Alliance, 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 25)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1934-1936 Annual Meetings, 1934-1936 (Box 62, Folder 26)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1937 Annual Meeting, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 27)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1938 Annual Meeting, 1938 (Box 62, Folder 28)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1939 Annual Meeting, 1939 (Box 62, Folder 29)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1940 Annual Meeting, 1940 (Box 62, Folder 30)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1941 Annual Meeting, 1941 (Box 62, Folder 31)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1942 Annual Meeting, 1942 (Box 62, Folder 32)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1944 Annual Meeting, 1944 (Box 62, Folder 33)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1945 Annual Meeting, 1945 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1946 Annual Meeting, 1945-1946, folder 1 of 2 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1946 Annual Meeting, 1945-1946, folder 2 of 2 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1947 Spring Meeting, 1946-1947, folder 1 of 2 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1947 Spring Meeting, 1946-1947, folder 2 of 2 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1948 Annual Meeting, 1947-1948 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1948 November Meeting, 1948 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1948 Spring Meeting - Correspondence with / re: Trustees, 1947-1948 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1948 Spring Meeting - Members' Reports, 1948 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1955 Spring Meeting, 1954-1955 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1956 Spring Meeting, 1956 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1956 Fall Meeting, 1955-1956 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1957 Fall Meeting, 1957 (Box 63, Folder 13)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1957 March Meeting, 1957 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1957 Meeting, 1957 (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1958 Fall Meeting, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1958 Spring Meeting, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 17)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1959 April Meeting, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1959 November Meeting, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 19)
- Virginia Art Alliance: 1960 April Meeting, 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 20)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Activities Reports 1956/57 Season, 1957 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Armed Forces Open Air Art Sale, 1944 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Articles, 1933-1936 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Attendance, 1956 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Board of Trustees, 1951 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Board of Trustees, 1952-1953 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Board of Trustees, 1952-1955 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Board of Trustees, 1956 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Catalogs of Exhibitions of Members, 1933-1942 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Catalogs of Exhibitions of Members, 1933-1942 (OVERSIZE) (Box 86, Folder 13)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Constitution and Preamble (Proposed), 1934 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Facilities Booklet, 1945 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Virginia Art Alliance: General, 1956-1960 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Minutes, 1934 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Newsletter, 1935-1937 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Newsletter, 1939 (Box 64, Folder 15)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Newsletter, 1939 (OVERSIZE) (Box 86, Folder 14)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Newsletter, 1941 (Box 64, Folder 16)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Newsletter - Material for, 1940 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Organization Data, 1934 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Procedures, undated (Box 64, Folder 19)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Reorganization, 1934-1937 (Box 64, Folder 20)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Reports of Group Members, 1955 (Box 64, Folder 21)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Southern Literary Messenger, 1940 (Box 64, Folder 22)
- Virginia Art Alliance: Trustees, 1934-1938 (Box 64, Folder 23)
- Virginia Art Commission, 1938-1951 (Box 64, Folder 24)
- Virginia Art Commission, 1938-1951 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 117)
- Virginia Art Commission, 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 25)
- Virginia Artists 1949, 1949 (Box 64, Folder 26)
- Virginia Artists 1955, 1954-1955 (Box 64, Folder 27)
- Virginia Artists 1967, 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 28)
- Virginia Artists 1969 May 5 - June 1, 1967-1968 (Box 64, Folder 29)
- Virginia Artists 1971, 1967-1971 (Box 64, Folder 30)
- Virginia Artists, 1973 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 118)
- Virginia Artists: Work Submitted for Pelligrini Publication, 1952 (Box 64, Folder 31)
- Virginia Artists Exhibition: Prospective Jurors, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 32)
- Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts, 1935-1943 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts, 1943-1952 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts: Audits, 1937-1956, folder 1 of 2 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts: Audits, 1937-1956, folder 2 of 2 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts: Systems Study, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Virginia Beach Boardwalk Show, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Virginia Center for Performing Arts, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Virginia Collections, 1935-1945 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Virginia Commission for the Arts, 1974-1975 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Virginia Commonwealth University, 1969-1972 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Virginia Commonwealth University, 1973-1975 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Virginia Craftsmen 1972, 1971-1972 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Virginia Department of Conservation and Development, 1946-1955 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Virginia Designers 1972, 1970-1972 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Virginia Division of Budget, 1946-1954 (Box 65, Folder 15)
- Virginia Drug Abuse Advisory Council: Ad Hoc Committee Report, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 16)
- Virginia Education Association, 1961-1965 (Box 65, Folder 17)
- Virginia Education Association, 1961-1965 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 119)
- Virginia Education Association: Art Section, 1934-1939 (Box 65, Folder 18)
- Virginia Education Association: Home for Retired Teachers, 1965 (Box 65, Folder 19)
- Virginia Federation of Women's Clubs, 1954-1970 (Box 65, Folder 20)
- Virginia Federation of Women's Clubs, 1967-1968 (Box 65, Folder 21)
- Virginia General Assembly: Thank Yous from Legislators, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 22)
- Virginia Governor: Battle, 1949-1953 (Box 65, Folder 23)
- Virginia Governor: Darden, 1945-1946 (Box 65, Folder 24)
- Virginia Governor: Peery, 1935-1938 (Box 65, Folder 25)
- Virginia Governor: Stanley, 1954-1955 (Box 65, Folder 26)
- Virginia Governor: Tuck, 1946-1950 (Box 65, Folder 27)
- Virginia Highlands Festival, 1952-1956 (Box 65, Folder 28)
- Virginia Historical Society, 1935-1945 (Box 65, Folder 29)
- Virginia Historical Society, 1935-1945 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 120)
- Virginia Historical Society, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 30)
- Virginia History Federation, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 31)
- Virginia Humanities Conference Meeting 1964, 1963-1964 (Box 65, Folder 32)
- Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission, 1970-1971 (Box 65, Folder 33)
- Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 34)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation, 1953-1954 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Agenda and Minutes of Meetings, 1953-1956 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Commission on Juvenile Delinquency, 1954-1955 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Correspondence, 1950-1956, folder 1 of 3 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Correspondence, 1950-1956, folder 2 of 3 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Correspondence, 1950-1956, folder 3 of 3 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Correspondence, 1950-1956 (OVERSIZE) (Box 86, Folder 15)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Dr. Pate's Report "Recreation as a Function of Government in Virginia", 1953 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Executive Order - Copies, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Film File, 1955-1956, folder 1 of 2 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Film File, 1955-1956, folder 2 of 2 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: First Report to the Governor, undated (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Legal Status in Counties, etc., 1954-1956 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Legislative, 1954-1956 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Lists, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Luray Conference, 1955-1956 (Box 66, Folder 15)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: National Recreation Association, 1948-1955 (Box 66, Folder 16)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: National Sports Month, 1955-1956 (Box 66, Folder 17)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Office Copies of Reference Publications, 1950-1954 (Box 66, Folder 18)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Ohio Conference, 1956 (Box 66, Folder 19)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Out-of-State Inter-Agencies on Recreation, 1953-1956 (Box 66, Folder 20)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Personnel and Purpose of, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 21)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Quotes, Clippings and Articles, 1953-1956 (Box 66, Folder 22)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Reference Manual, 1950-1955 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Regional Conferences, 1955-1956 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Reports and Publications, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Second Report to the Governor, 1955-1956 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Southern Regional Education Board, 1954-1955 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation: Virginia Art Alliance, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Virginia Interior Designers 1971, 1970-1971 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Virginia Legislature, 1960-1969 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Virginia Municipal League, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Ambrose, Faye, 1956-1957 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Baker, Charles Ewert, 1950-1951 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Bartley, Regina, 1951-1952 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Bland, William Thomas, 1948-1950 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Brushwood, Robert, 1955-1956 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Caldwell, Kuhn R., 1955-1957 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Carter, Thomas R., 1950-1951 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Cheatham, Mary Frances, 1948-1952 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Clausen, Janet B., 1953-1955 (Box 68, Folder 12)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Darden, William D., 1950-1951 (Box 68, Folder 13)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Davis, Robert Lawson, 1953-1954 (Box 68, Folder 14)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Day, Worden, 1949-1950 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Downing, T.V., Jr., 1949-1954 (Box 68, Folder 16)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Flynn, Charles, Jr., 1951-1952 (Box 68, Folder 17)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Franklin, Jenny-Lynn, 1953-1954 (Box 68, Folder 18)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Franklin, Jenny-Lynn, 1954-1955 (Box 68, Folder 19)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Franklin, Jenny-Lynn, 1955-1956 (Box 68, Folder 20)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Gaines, William R., 1949-1951 (Box 68, Folder 21)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Harding, Barbara, 1953-1955 (Box 68, Folder 22)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Hipp, Catherine Marie, 1952-1953 (Box 68, Folder 23)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Hom, Jem W., 1956-1957 (Box 68, Folder 24)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Houghland, Wright B., 1955-1956 (Box 68, Folder 25)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Huff, Cecile Caroline, 1953-1954 (Box 68, Folder 26)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Jackson, William Ward, 1948-1955 (Box 68, Folder 27)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Knapp, Benjamin, 1953-1954 (Box 68, Folder 28)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Leedy, James, 1957-1958 (Box 68, Folder 29)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: MacBaisry, Brenda R., 1955-1956 (Box 68, Folder 30)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: MacBaisry, Brenda R., 1955-1956 (OVERSIZE) (Box 86, Folder 16)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Moyers, James Piper, 1953-1954 (Box 68, Folder 31)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Ravenscroft, Joe, 1952-1953 (Box 68, Folder 32)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Reinhart, Marnye, 1948-1949 [1] (Box 68, Folder 33)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Reinhart, Marnye, 1948-1949 [2] (Box 68, Folder 34)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Russell, Milo F., 1955-1956 (Box 68, Folder 35)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Spain, Raymond E., 1955-1956 (Box 68, Folder 36)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Tatum, Mary R., 1951-1952 (Box 68, Folder 37)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Turner, Primm, 1956-1957 (Box 68, Folder 38)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Twombly, E. Parker, 1952-1953 (Box 68, Folder 39)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Twombly, Edwin Parker, Jr., 1950-1951 (Box 68, Folder 40)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Wigfall, Benjamin, 1949-1950 (Box 68, Folder 41)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Wigfall, Benjamin, 1951-1952 (Box 68, Folder 42)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Wigfall, Benjamin, 1952-1953 (Box 68, Folder 43)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Woody, Howard, 1954-1955 (Box 68, Folder 44)
- Virginia Museum Fellowship: Wreden, Peter, 1953-1954 (Box 68, Folder 45)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Applications, 1946-1947 [1] (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Applications, 1946-1947 [2] (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Applications, 1947-1948 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Applications, 1948-1949 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Applications, 1949-1950 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Applications, 1950-1951, folder 1 of 2 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Applications, 1950-1951, folder 2 of 2 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Applications, 1951-1952 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Applications, 1952-1953 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Applications, 1953-1954 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Applications, 1954-1955, folder 1 of 2 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Applications, 1954-1955, folder 2 of 2 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Applications, 1955-1956, folder 1 of 3 (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Applications, 1955-1956, folder 2 of 3 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Applications, 1955-1956, folder 3 of 3 (Box 69, Folder 15)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Correspondence with Mr. Pratt, 1940-1954 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Correspondence with Mr. Pratt, 1940-1954 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 121)